Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College student records
1901-2007
RU 587
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
901.67
(1,025 boxes)
The records consist of student records and grade sheets maintained by Yale College.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-F (YRG 9-F), Yale College student records.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records and grade sheets maintained by Yale College.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Students
- Student record cards for the Classes of 1947 and 1949M, 1943-1949; Accession 1950-A-003
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Professional interests/plans cards for Class of 1947
  - Student records for Class of 1949M
- Student records for the Classes of 1947-1960, 1943-1960; Accession 1961-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Class of 1947N
  - Moore - Moses, 1950 (Box 34A)
- Student records for the Classes of 1961-1963, 1957-1963; Accession 1964-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by class year, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - Class of 1961
  - Class of 1962
  - Class of 1963
  - Ex-students from Classes of 1961-1963
- Student records for the Classes of 1940-1955, 1936-1955; Accession 1974-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
- Student record cards for the Classes of 1931-1956, 1927-1956; Accession 1987-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  - A - G, 1931 (Box 1)
  - H - M, 1931 (Box 2)
  - M - S, 1931 (Box 3)
  - S - Z, 1931 (Box 4)
  - A - C, 1932 (Box 4)
  - C - H, 1932 (Box 5)
  - J - M, 1932 (Box 6)
  - A - C, 1934 (Box 6)
  - C - I, 1934 (Box 7)
  - J - Q, 1934 (Box 8)
  - R - Z, 1934 (Box 9)
  - A - C, 1935 (Box 10)
  - C - K, 1935 (Box 11)
  - L - S, 1935 (Box 12)
  - S - Z, 1935 (Box 13)
  - A - B, 1936 (Box 13)
  - B - H, 1936 (Box 14)
  - H - M, 1936 (Box 15)
  - O - Z, 1936 (Box 16)
  - A - F, 1937 (Box 17)
  - F - M, 1937 (Box 18)
  - M - Z, 1937 (Box 19)
  - A - H, 1938 (Box 20)
  - H - S, 1938 (Box 21)
  - S - Z, 1938 (Box 22)
  - A - G, 1939 (Box 23)
  - G - P, 1939 (Box 24)
  - P - Z, 1939 (Box 25)
  - A - B, 1940 (Box 25)
  - C - J, 1940 (Box 26)
  - K - S, 1940 (Box 27)
  - S - Z, 1940 (Box 28)
  - Class of 1940
  - Class of 1941
    - A - C, 1941 (Box 28)
    - C - L, 1941 (Box 29)
    - M - Z, 1941
  - Class of 1942
  - Class of 1943
  - A - G, 1942 (Box 31)
  - G - N, 1942 (Box 32)
  - P - Z, 1942 (Box 33)
  - A - D, 1943 (Box 33)
  - E - M, 1943 (Box 34)
  - M - T, 1943 (Box 35)
  - T - W, 1943 (Box 36)
  - A - F, 1944 (Box 36)
  - F - P, 1944 (Box 37)
  - Q - Z, 1944 (Box 38)
  - A - B, 1945 (Box 38)
  - C - M, 1945 (Box 39)
  - P - Z, 1945 (Box 40)
  - A - B, 1945W (Box 40)
  - C - N, 1945W (Box 41)
  - O - W, 1945W (Box 42)
  - A - Z, 1945WF (Box 42)
  - A - W, 1945WO (Box 43)
  - A - C, 1946 (Box 43)
  - C - R, 1946 (Box 44)
  - R - Z, 1946 (Box 45)
  - A - F, 1946M (Box 45)
  - G - V, 1946M (Box 46)
  - W - Z, 1946M (Box 47)
  - A - N, 1946N (Box 47)
  - O -Z, 1946N (Box 48)
  - A - B, 1947 (Box 48)
  - B - H, 1947 (Box 49)
  - H - P, 1947 (Box 50)
  - P - V, 1947 (Box 51)
  - W - Z, 1947 (Box 52)
  - A - C, 1947M (Box 52)
  - D - J, 1947M (Box 53)
  - K - P, 1947M (Box 54)
  - Q - W, 1947M (Box 55)
  - W - Z, 1947M (Box 56)
  - A - M, 1947N (Box 56)
  - N - Z, 1947N (Box 57)
  - A - D, 1948 (Box 57)
  - D - R, 1948 (Box 58)
  - R - Z, 1948 (Box 59)
  - A - B, 1949 (Box 59)
  - B - F, 1949 (Box 60)
  - F - J, 1949 (Box 61)
  - K - N, 1949 (Box 62)
  - O - S, 1949 (Box 63)
  - S - Z, 1949 (Box 64)
  - A, 1950 (Box 64)
  - B - C, 1950 (Box 65)
  - D - G, 1950 (Box 66)
  - G - K, 1950 (Box 67)
  - K - M, 1950 (Box 68)
  - M - S, 1950 (Box 69)
  - S - Z, 1950 (Box 70)
  - A -F, 1951 (Box 71)
  - F - M, 1951 (Box 72)
  - M - T, 1951 (Box 73)
  - T - Z, 1951 (Box 74)
  - A - C, 1952 (Box 74)
  - C - I, 1952 (Box 75)
  - J - P, 1952 (Box 76)
  - P - W, 1952 (Box 77)
  - W - Z, 1952 (Box 78)
  - A - D, 1953 (Box 78)
  - D - K, 1953 (Box 79)
  - L - R, 1953 (Box 80)
  - S - Z, 1953 (Box 81)
  - A - D, 1954 (Box 82)
  - D - L, 1954 (Box 83)
  - L - R, 1954 (Box 84)
  - R - Z, 1954 (Box 85)
  - A - D, 1955 (Box 86)
  - D - J, 1955 (Box 87)
  - K - O, 1955 (Box 88)
  - P - T, 1955 (Box 89)
  - U - Z, 1955 (Box 90)
  - A - D, misc., 1956 (Box 90)
- Matriculation cards for students in the Classes of 1972 and 1974, 1968-1974; Accession 1990-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  - A - O, 1972 (Box 1)
  - P - Z, 1972 (Box 2)
  - A - C, 1974 (Box 3)
  - D - G, 1974 (Box 4)
  - H - K, 1974 (Box 5)
  - L - O, 1974 (Box 6)
  - P - SP, 1974 (Box 7)
  - ST - XYZ, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Withdrawals A - Z, 1974 (Box 9)
- Student record cards for the Classes of 1932-1939, 1960-1969, 1928-1939, 1956-1969; Accession 1987-A-035
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - A - K, 1932 (Box 1)
  - L - Z, 1932 (Box 2)
  - Ex-students A - W, 1932 (Box 3)
  - A - Gar, 1933 (Box 3)
  - Gas - S, 1933 (Box 4)
  - T - Z, 1933 (Box 5)
  - Ex-students A - Y, 1933 (Box 5)
  - A - D, 1934 (Box 5)
  - E - Se, 1934 (Box 6)
  - Sh - Z, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Ex-students A - W, 1934 (Box 7)
  - A - Bo, 1935 (Box 7)
  - Br - R, 1935 (Box 8)
  - S - Z, 1935 (Box 9)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1935 (Box 9)
  - A - B, 1936 (Box 9)
  - C - Ra, 1936 (Box 10)
  - Re -, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1936 (Box 11)
  - A, 1937 (Box 11)
  - B - Ma, 1937 (Box 12)
  - Me - Z, 1937 (Box 13)
  - Ex-students A - R, 1937 (Box 13)
  - Ex-students S - W, 1937 (Box 14)
  - A - Ma, 1938 (Box 14)
  - Me - Y, 1938 (Box 15)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1938 (Box 15)
  - A - K, 1939 (Box 16)
  - L - Z, 1939 (Box 17)
  - Ex-students A - Ho, 1939 (Box 17)
  - Ex-students Hu - W, 1939 (Box 18)
  - A - D, 1960 (Box 19)
  - E - L, 1960 (Box 20)
  - Mc - Sn, 1960 (Box 21)
  - So - Z, 1960 (Box 22)
  - Ex-students A - Y, 1960 (Box 22)
  - A - E, 1961 (Box 23)
  - F - Lo, 1961 (Box 24)
  - Lu - Sch, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Sh - Z, 1961 (Box 26)
  - Ex-students B - L, 1961 (Box 26)
  - Ex-students M - W, 1961 (Box 27)
  - A - Do, 1962 (Box 27)
  - Du - La, 1962 (Box 28)
  - Le - R, 1962 (Box 29)
  - S - Z, 1962 (Box 30)
  - Ex-students B - Z, 1962 (Box 31)
  - A - Cr, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Cu - J, 1963 (Box 32)
  - K - Re, 1963 (Box 33)
  - Rh - Whe, 1963 (Box 34)
  - Whi - Z, 1963 (Box 35)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1963 (Box 35)
  - A - Sce, 1964 (Box 35a)
  - Sco - Z, 1964 (Box 36)
  - Ex-students A - Y, 1964 (Box 37)
  - A - C, 1965 (Box 37)
  - D - Ja, 1965 (Box 38)
  - Je - Pet, 1965 (Box 39)
  - Ph - Tr, 1965 (Box 40)
  - Ts - Z, 1965 (Box 41)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1965 (Box 41)
  - A - Ba, 1966 (Box 41)
  - Be - Fu, 1966 (Box 42)
  - G - Li, 1966 (Box 43)
  - Ll - Sa, 1966 (Box 44)
  - Sc - Z, 1966 (Box 45)
  - Ex-students A - W, 1966 (Box 46)
  - A - E, 1966 (Box 46)
  - F - R, 1966 (Box 47)
  - Sa - Z, 1966 (Box 48)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1966 (Box 48)
  - A - Ch, 1967 (Box 48)
  - Cl - N, 1967 (Box 49)
  - O - Z, 1967 (Box 50)
  - Ex-students A - W, 1967 (Box 50)
  - A - Ga, 1967 (Box 51)
  - Ge - Mi, 1967 (Box 52)
  - Mo - Wa, 1967 (Box 53)
  - We - Z, 1967 (Box 54)
  - Ex-students A - W, 1967 (Box 54)
  - A - Br, 1968 (Box 54)
  - Bu - He, 1968 (Box 55)
  - Hi - No, 1968 (Box 56)
  - O - T, 1968 (Box 57)
  - V - Z, 1968 (Box 58)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1968 (Box 58)
  - A - Ch, 1968 (Box 58)
  - Cl - Le, 1968 (Box 59)
  - Li - T, 1968 (Box 60)
  - U - Z, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1968 (Box 61)
  - A - F, 1969 (Box 61)
  - G - S, 1969 (Box 62)
  - T - Z, 1969 (Box 63)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1969 (Box 63)
  - A - Bu, 1969 (Box 63)
  - C - Ha, 1969 (Box 64)
  - He - Mo, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Mu - Sw, 1969 (Box 66)
  - T - Z, 1969 (Box 67)
  - Ex-students A - Z, 1969 (Box 67)
- Student records for the Classes of 1975-1977, 1971-1977; Accession 1993-A-069
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  - HUDSON, DF; Saybrook College, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 501)
  - Friedman, AC; Berkeley College, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1751)
  - BERANBAUM, JA; Jonathan Edwards, 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 2876)
  - THIGPEN, TP; Saybrook College, 1973-1977 (Box 18A, Folder 3939)
- Student records for the Classes of 1980-1986, 1976-1986; Accession 1997-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
- Student records for the Classes of 1978-1979, Accession 1998-A-065
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - Fotos, M.A., 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 500)
  - Etzwiler, Nancy Grey, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1750)
  - Out/Withdrawals, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2690)
- Registrar folders for the Classes of 1979-1996, 1975-1996; Accession 2000-A-057
  Arranged by class, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - Class of 1979
    - Alb-Cam (Box 1)
    - Cam-Duv (Box 2)
    - Eal-Gut (Box 3)
    - Hai-Kra (Box 4)
    - Kri-Mof (Box 5)
    - Mok-Rin (Box 6)
    - Rin-Tom (Box 7)
    - Ton-Zur (Box 8)
  - Class of 1980
    - Abe-Bar (Box 8)
    - Bar-Del (Box 9)
    - Del-Hee (Box 10)
    - Hel-Lyd (Box 11)
    - Lyn-Res (Box 12)
    - Res-Tow (Box 13)
    - Tri-Zyo (Box 14)
  - Class of 1981
    - Abe-Bas (Box 14)
    - Bau-Far (Box 15)
    - Far-Jon (Box 16)
    - Joy-Mer (Box 17)
    - Mer-Rod (Box 18)
    - Rod-Tit (Box 19)
    - Tit-Zuc (Box 20)
  - Class of 1982
    - Ada-Fer (Box 21)
    - Fie-Lus (Box 22)
    - Lut-Sma (Box 23)
    - Sma-Zuc (Box 24)
  - Class of 1983
    - Abe-Brooks (Box 24)
    - Brop-Goo (Box 25)
    - Gop-Mac (Box 26)
    - Mad-Sal (Box 27)
    - Saleh-Zwe (Box 28)
  - Class of 1984
    - Abr-Eck (Box 29)
    - Ede-Knit (Box 30)
    - Koc-Pom (Box 31)
    - Pon-Web (Box 32)
    - Wec-Zy (Box 33)
  - Class of 1985
    - Aar-Dic (Box 33)
    - Dick-Lama (Box 34)
    - Lamb-Rya (Box 35)
    - Sac-Zor (Box 36)
  - Class of 1986
    - Abo-Bak (Box 36)
    - Bal-Garc (Box 37)
    - Gard-Mer (Box 38)
    - Mes-Solom (Box 39)
    - Solov-Z (Box 40)
  - Class of 1987 (Box 40)
    - Abl-Gar (Box 41)
    - Gas-Matt (Box 42)
    - Matz-Sza (Box 43)
    - Tag-Zur (Box 44)
  - Class of 1988
    - Abe-Calla (Box 44)
    - Calle-Hom (Box 45)
    - Hoo-Ng (Box 46)
    - Ngu-Val (Box 47)
    - Van-Zym (Box 48)
  - Class of 1989
    - Abb-Coh (Box 48)
    - Col-Johnson, O. (Box 49)
  - Class of 1990
    - Aam-Ede (Box 52)
    - Ede-Lun (Box 53)
  - Class of 1991
    - Abd-Gur (Box 56)
    - Gut-Parsk (Box 57)
    - Parso-Zul (Box 58)
  - Class of 1993
    - Ada-Gar (Box 59)
    - Gat-Mald (Box 60)
    - Mali-Stae (Box 61)
    - Stat-Zwe (Box 62)
  - Class of 1994
    - Abu-Cop (Box 62)
    - Cor-Lee (Box 63)
    - Leh-Silb (Box 64)
    - Silv-Zur (Box 65)
  - Class of 1995
    - Ack-Dac (Box 65)
    - Dai-Lou (Box 66)
    - Low-Sun (Box 67)
    - Suns-Zla (Box 68)
  - Class of 1996
    - Abd-Cob (Box 68)
    - Coe-Log (Box 69)
- Student records of the dean for the Classes of 1987-1991, 1983-1991 inclusive; Accession 2001-A-030
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - Class of 1987
    - A-B, 1983-1987 (Box 1)
    - C-D, 1983-1987 (Box 2)
    - E-G, 1983-1987 (Box 3)
    - H-J, 1983-1987 (Box 4)
    - K-Mau, 1983-1987 (Box 5)
    - Me-P, 1983-1987 (Box 6)
    - Q-So, 1983-1987 (Box 7)
    - Sp-V, 1983-1987 (Box 8)
    - W-Z, 1983-1987 (Box 9)
    - Non-graduates, 1983-1987 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1988
    - A-Cho, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
    - Chu-Ge, 1984-1988 (Box 11)
    - Gi-Ker, 1984-1988 (Box 12)
    - Key-Melb, 1984-1988 (Box 13)
    - Melc-Pos, 1984-1988 (Box 14)
    - Pow-Stel, 1984-1988 (Box 15)
    - Ster-Z, 1984-1988 (Box 16)
  - Class of 1989
    - Non-graduates and withdraws, 1985-1989 (Box 23)
  - Class of 1990
  - Class of 1991
    - The Schuman Plan--A Preliminary Prediction,. Vol. VI, No. 3, 1987-1991 (Box 38)
    - Non-graduates, 1987-1991 (Box 38)
- High school grade cards for admitted students, circa 1930-1955; Accession 2001-A-067
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Barbee, Robert Allen, 1950 (Box 1)
- Entrance cards (high school grade cards) and duplicate freshman year cards, 1936-1956; Accession 2001-A-140
- Student entrance records for the Classes of 1904-1939, 1900-1935 inclusive; Accession 2002-A-002
  The materials are open for research.
  - Classes of 1904-1908
    - Ace-Spe (Box 1)
    - Sta-Z (Box 2)
  - Classes of 1908-1914
    - A-Gow (Box 2)
    - Gra-Q (Box 3)
    - R-Z (Box 4)
  - Classes of 1924, 1925
    - A-Gro (Box 5)
    - Gue-Z (Box 6)
  - Class of 1926 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1924-1926 ex (Box 8)
  - Class of 1927 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1928
    - A-R (Box 10)
    - S-Z (Box 11)
  - Class of 1929
    - A-K (Box 11)
    - L-Z (Box 12)
  - Class of 1930
    - A-Dou (Box 12)
    - Dre-Y (Box 13)
  - Class of 1931
    - A-R (Box 14)
    - S-Z (Box 15)
  - Class of 1932
    - A-K (Box 15)
    - L-Z (Box 16)
  - Class of 1933
  - A-Gli (Box 16)
    - Gol-Z (Box 17)
  - Class of 1934
    - A-B (Box 17)
    - C-Z (Box 18)
  - Class of 1935 (Box 19)
  - Class of 1936 (Box 20)
  - Class of 1937 (Box 21)
  - Class of 1938 (Box 22)
  - Class of 1939
    - A-Che (Box 22)
    - Clo-Z (Box 23)
- Scholarship record cards, circa 1903-1929; Accession 2002-A-003
  - Class of 1906 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1907
    - A-G (Box 1)
    - H-Y (Box 2)
  - Class of 1908
    - A-K (Box 2)
    - L-Y (Box 3)
  - Class of 1909
    - A-Smi (Box 3)
    - Sou-Z (Box 4)
  - Class of 1910 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1911
    - A-C (Box 4)
    - D-Y (Box 5)
  - Class of 1912
    - A-L (Box 5)
    - M-Y (Box 6)
  - Class of 1913
    - A-V (Box 6)
    - W-Y (Box 7)
  - Class of 1914 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1915
    - A-Dai (Box 7)
    - Dau-Dar (Box 8)
  - Class of 1916
    - A-Gru (Box 8)
    - Gue-Z (Box 9)
  - Class of 1917
    - A-H (Box 9)
    - I-Z (Box 10)
  - Class of 1918
    - A-H (Box 10)
    - I-Y (Box 11)
  - Class of 1919
    - A-H (Box 11)
    - I-Y (Box 12)
  - Class of 1920
    - A-M (Box 12)
    - N-Y (Box 13)
  - Class of 1921 (Box 13)
  - Class of 1922
    - A-C (Box 13)
    - D-W (Box 14)
    - Yale Army Training Corps and Yale Naval Training Unit (Box 14)
  - Class of 1923 (Box 15)
  - Class of 1924 (Box 16)
  - Class of 1925
    - A-Boy (Box 16)
    - Bra-Z (Box 17)
  - Class of 1926
    - A-Spe (Box 18)
    - Sta-Z (Box 19)
  - Class of 1927
    - A-Mit (Box 19)
    - Moo-Y (Box 20)
  - Class of 1928
    - A-Gos (Box 20)
    - Gra-Z (Box 21)
  - Class of 1929
    - A-P (Box 22)
    - R-Z (Box 23)
- Yale studies for returning servicemen, 1943-1946; Accession 2002-A-004 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  No inventory available.
- Student transcripts for the Classes of 1954-1977, 1951-1977; Accession 2002-A-007
  - Classes of 1954, 1954e, 1955, 1955e, 1956, 1956e (Box 16)
  - Class of 1957
    - A-N (Box 16)
    - O-Z (Box 17)
  - Classes of 1957-ex, 1958, 1958-ex, 1959, 1959-ex, 1960, 1960-ex (Box 17)
  - Class of 1961
    - A-G (Box 17)
    - H-Z, ex-students (Box 18)
  - Classes of 1962, 1962-ex, 1963, 1963-ex (Box 18)
  - Class of 1964
    - A-R (Box 18)
    - S-Z (Sad-Twi not in folders), ex-students (Box 19)
  - Classes of 1965, 1965-ex, 1966, 1966-ex (Box 19)
  - Class of 1967
    - A-L (Box 19)
    - M-Z, ex-students (Box 20)
  - Classes of 1968, 1968-ex, 1969, 1969-ex (Box 20)
  - Class of 1970
    - A-E (Box 20)
    - F-Z (Box 21)
  - Class of 1971 (and its questionnaire preference) (Box 21)
  - Class of 1972 (including college credits awarded)
    - A-L (Box 21)
    - M-Z (Box 22)
  - Classes of 1973, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Classes of 1975 -1976 (including college credits awarded) (Box 23)
  - Class of 1977
    - A-F (Box 23)
    - G-Z (Box 24)
  - Class of 1978 (Box 24)
  - Class of 1956 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1957
    - A-Pie (Box 2)
    - Pil-Z (Box 3)
  - Class of 1958
    - A-Hol (Box 3)
    - Holn-Z (Box 4)
  - Class of 1959
    - A-Ott (not in folders) (Box 6)
    - Pag-Z (Box 7)
  - Class of 1960 (not in folders)
    - A-Gor (Box 7)
    - Gos-Z (Box 8)
  - Class of 1961
    - Roo-Z, Withdrawals (Box 10)
  - Class of 1962
    - A-Mei (Box 10)
    - Mel-Z (Box 11)
  - Class of 1963
  - A-Lil (Box 11)
    - Lin-Z (Box 12)
  - Class of 1964
    - B-Gil (Box 12)
    - Gill-Y (Box 13)
  - Class of 1965
    - A-Ord (Box 14)
  - Ort-Z (Box 15)
- Admission data cards and entrance records for the Classes of 1956-1993, 1952-1993; Accession 2002-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Classes of 1956, 1957, and Special students, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1956
    - A-Spe (Box 2)
    - Spo-Z, ex-students (transcripts) (Box 3)
  - Class of 1957
    - A-Rob (transcripts) (Box 3)
    - Rog-Z, ex-students (Box 4)
  - Class of 1958
    - A-Ken (Box 4)
    - Ker-Z, ex-students (Box 5)
  - Class of 1959
    - A-Be (Box 5)
    - Deu-Z, ex-students (Box 6)
  - Class of 1984
  - Classes of 1959, 1960, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1962
    - A-M (Box 7)
    - N-Z (Box 8)
  - Classes of 1963, 1964, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1966
    - A-M (Box 8)
    - N-Z (Box 9)
  - Classes of 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Class of 1970
    - A-L (Box 9)
    - M-Z (Box 10)
  - Classes of 1971, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Class of 1973
    - A-R (Box 10)
    - S-Z (Box 11)
  - Classes of 1974, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Class of 1976
    - A-M (Box 11)
    - N-Z (Box 12)
  - Classes of 1977, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1979
    - A-Pet (Box 12)
    - Pew-Z (Box 13)
  - Class of 1980 (Box 13)
  - Classes of 1981, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1983
    - A-Fin (Box 14)
    - Fis-Z (Box 15)
  - Class of 1984 (Box 15)
  - Class of 1980 (Box 15)
  - Classes of 1987, 1989: A-Leb; Report dated 1990 for Class of 1993[?] (Box 16)
  - Class of 1989: Lew-Z; Report dated 1990 for Class of 1993[?] (Box 17)
- Grade lists and grade change records, 1901-1996; Accession 2004-A-073
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1901 Fall -1902 Spring (Box 1)
  - 1902 Fall - 1903 Spring (Box 1)
  - 1903 Fall - 1904 Spring (Box 1)
  - 1904 Fall - 1905 Spring (Box 2)
  - 1905 Fall - 1906 Spring (Box 2)
  - 1906 Fall - 1907 Spring (Box 2)
  - 1907 Fall - 1908 Spring (Box 3)
  - 1908 Fall - 1909 Spring (Box 3)
  - 1909 Fall - 1910 Spring (Box 3)
  - 1910 Fall - 1911 Spring (Box 4)
  - 1911 Fall - 1912 Spring (Box 4)
  - 1912 Fall - 1913 Spring (Box 4)
  - 1913 Fall - 1914 Spring (Box 5)
  - 1914 Fall - 1915 Spring (Box 5)
  - 1915 Fall - 1916 Spring (Box 5)
  - 1920 Fall - 1921 Spring and Law 1921 (Box 6)
  - 1921 Fall - 1922 Spring (Box 6)
  - 1922 Fall - 1923 Spring (Box 6)
  - 1923 Fall - 1924 Spring (Box 7)
  - 1924 Fall - 1925 Spring (Box 7)
  - 1925 Fall - 1926 Spring (Box 7)
  - 1926 Fall - 1927 Spring (Box 8)
  - 1927 Fall - 1928 Spring (Box 8)
  - 1928 Fall - 1929 Spring (Box 8)
  - 1929 Fall - 1930 Spring (Box 9)
  - 1930 Fall - 1931 Spring (Box 9)
  - 1932 Spring and 1933 Spring (Box 9)
  - 1934 Spring and 1935 Spring (Box 10)
  - 1936 Spring and 1937 Spring (Box 10)
  - 1938 Spring and 1939 Spring (Box 10)
  - 1940 Spring and 1941 Spring (Box 11)
  - 1942 Spring (Jun and Sep) - 1942 Fall (Box 11)
  - 1943 Jan, May, Oct and Dec (Box 11)
  - 1944 Jun, Aug, Oct, Feb 1945 (Box 12)
  - 1945 Spring (Jun and Oct) - 1945 Fall (Box 12)
  - 1946 Spring (Box 12)
  - 1946 Summer - 1946 Fall (Box 13)
  - 1947 Spring - 1947 Summer (Box 13)
  - 1947 Fall (Box 13)
  - 1948 Spring and 1948 DE Grades (Box 14)
  - 1948 Fall (Box 14)
  - 1949 Spring (A-K only) and 1949 DE Grades (Box 14)
  - 1949 Fall (Box 14)
  - 1950 Spring (Box 15)
  - 1950 Fall - 1951 Spring (Box 15)
  - 1951 Fall - 1952 Spring (A-K) (Box 15)
  - 1952 Spring (L-Z) - 1952 Fall (Box 16)
  - 1953 DE Grades and 1953 Spring (Box 16)
  - 1953 Fall - 1954 Spring and 1954 DE Grades (Box 16)
  - 1954 Fall - 1955 Spring - 1955 Fall and 1955 DE Grades (Box 17)
  - 1956 DE Grades and 1956 Spring (Box 17)
  - 1956 Fall - 1957 Spring (A-Hist) (Box 18)
  - 1957 Spring (Hist Art - Z) - 1957 Fall (Box 18)
  - 1957 DE Grades (Box 18)
  - 1958 Spring and 1958 DE Grades (Box 18)
  - 1958 Fall - 1959 Spring (A - Hist) (Box 19)
  - 1959 Spring (Hist Art - Z) - 1959 Fall (Box 19)
  - 1959 DE Grades (Box 19)
  - 1960 DE Grades and 1960 Fall (A - G) (Box 19)
  - 1960 Fall (H - Z) - 1961 Spring (Box 20)
  - 1961 DE Grades (Box 20)
  - 1961 Fall - 1962 Spring (A - Hist) (Box 20)
  - 1962 Spring (Hist Art - Z) - 1962 Fall (Box 20)
  - 1962 DE Grades and 1962 Grade Changes (Box 20)
  - 1962 Fall Changes/Makeup and 1963 June and Sept Makeups and 1963 Grade Changes (Box 21)
  - 1963 Spring and 1963 DE Grades (Box 21)
  - 1962-1963 Class of 1966 (Box 21)
  - 1963-1964 Class of 1967 (Box 21)
  - 1963 Fall (Box 21)
  - 1963 Fall Changes (Box 22)
  - 1964 Spring (Box 22)
  - 1963-1964 Changes and 1964 DE Grades (Box 22)
  - 1964 Fall (Box 22)
  - 1965 Spring (Box 23)
  - 1964-1965 Grade Changes (Box 23)
  - 1966 Jan Makeups (Box 23)
  - 1965 Fall - 1966 Spring (Box 24)
  - 1964-1965 Class of 1968 (Box 24)
  - 1964-1965 Class of 1969 (Box 25)
  - 1966 Fall - 1967 Spring - 1967 Fall (Box 25)
  - 1966-1967 Class of 1970 (Box 26)
  - 1967-1968 Class of 1971 (Box 26)
  - 1968 Spring - 1968 Fall (Box 26)
  - 1968-1969 Class of 1972 (Box 26)
  - 1968-1969 Grade Changes (Box 27)
  - 1969 Spring (See Box 29) (Box 28)
  - 1970 Spring - 1970 Fall (Box 28)
  - 1969 Spring -Class of 1970 (Box 29)
  - 1969 Fall - 1971 Spring (Box 29)
  - 1969-1970 - Class of 1973 (Box 29)
  - 1969 Fall Grade Changes (Box 30)
  - 1970 Spring Grade Changes (Box 31)
  - 1971-1972 Grade Changes (Box 31)
  - 1970 Fall Grade Changes (Box 32)
  - 1971 Spring Grade Changes (Box 32)
  - 1971 Fall Grade Changes (Box 32)
  - 1970-1971 - Class of 1974 (Box 33)
  - 1971 Fall (Box 33)
  - 1971-1972 - Class of 1975 (Box 33)
  - 1972 Fall - Class of 76 (Box 33)
  - 1972 Spring - 1972 Fall (Box 34)
  - 1973 Spring (Box 35)
  - 1973 Spring - Class of 1976 (Box 35)
  - 1973 DE (Box 35)
  - 1973 Fall (Box 36)
  - 1973-1974 - Class of 1977 (Box 36)
  - 1974 DE Exams (Box 37)
  - 1974 Spring (Box 37)
  - 1974 Spring - Class of 1974 (Box 37)
  - 1974 Fall - 1975 Spring A - G (Box 38)
  - 1975 Spring H - Z (Box 39)
  - 1975 Fall (Box 39)
  - 1975 DE Exams (Box 39)
  - 1976 Spring (Box 40)
  - 1975 Fall - 1977 Spring - Class of 1979 (Box 41)
  - 1972 Spring through Fall 1975 Grade Changes (Box 41)
  - 1976 Fall (Box 42)
  - 1977 Spring (Box 43)
  - 1976-1977 Grade Changes (Box 44)
  - 1977 Fall (Box 45)
  - 1978 Spring A - L (Box 46)
  - 1978 Spring M - Z (Box 47)
  - 1978 Fall A - F (Box 47)
  - 1978 Fall G - Z (Box 48)
  - 1979 Spring A - Engin (Box 48)
  - 1979 Spring Engl - Z (Box 49)
  - 1979 Fall (Box 50)
  - 1980 Spring A - M (Box 51)
  - 1980 Spring N - Z (Box 52)
  - 1980 Fall - A - L (Box 52)
  - 1980 Fall M - Z (Box 53)
  - 1981 Spring A - L (Box 53)
  - 1981 Spring M - Z (Box 54)
  - 1981 Fall A - H (Box 54)
  - 1981 Fall I - Z (Box 55)
  - 1982 Spring A - H (Box 55)
  - 1982 Spring I - Z (Box 56)
  - 1982 Fall A - G (Box 56)
  - 1982 Fall H - Z (Box 57)
  - 1983 Spring A - G (Box 57)
  - 1983 Spring H - Z (Box 58)
  - 1983 Fall A -G (Box 58)
  - 1983 Fall H - Z (Box 59)
  - 1984 Spring A - G (Box 59)
  - 1984 Spring H - Z (Box 60)
  - 1984 Fall A - G (Box 60)
  - 1984 Fall H - Z (Box 61)
  - 1985 Spring A - G (Box 61)
  - 1985 Spring H - Z (Box 62)
  - 1985 Fall A - E (Box 62)
  - 1985 Fall F - Z (Box 63)
  - 1986 Spring A - E (Box 63)
  - 1986 Spring F - Z (Box 64)
  - 1986 Fall A - B (Box 64)
  - 1986 Fall C - Z (Box 65)
  - 1987 Spring A - B (Box 65)
  - 1987 Spring C - Z (Box 66)
  - 1987 Fall (Box 67)
  - Class of 1988 (Box 68)
  - 1988 Final Compilations - Spring (Box 68)
  - 1988 Spring A - F (Box 68)
  - 1988 Spring G - Z (Box 69)
  - 1989 Fall (Box 70)
  - 1989 Spring A - Psych (Box 71)
  - 1989 Spring Rel.St. - Z (Box 72)
  - 1989 Fall (Box 72)
  - 1990 Spring A - Psych (Box 73)
  - 1990 Spring Rel. St. - Z (Box 74)
  - 1990 Fall (Box 74)
  - 1991 Spring A - P (Box 75)
  - 1991 Spring R - Z (Box 76)
  - 1991 Fall (Box 76)
  - 1992 Spring A - R (Box 77)
  - 1992 Spring S - Z (Box 78)
  - 1992 Fall (Box 78)